Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 1977/78
    - Centers/Programs
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 281)
      - English Composition Board (Box 281)
      - Human Growth and Development (Box 281)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 281)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 281)
      - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 281)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (Box 281)
      - Near Eastern and North African Studies (Box 281)
      - Pilot Program (Box 281)
      - Population Studies (Box 281)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 281)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Box 281)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 281)
      - Western European Studies (Box 281)
      - Women's Studies (Box 281)
    - Museums
      - General (Box 281)
      - Anthropology (Box 281)
      - Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 281)
      - Art (Box 281)
      - Exhibits (Box 281)
      - Paleontology (Box 281)
      - Zoology (Box 281)
    - Laboratories/Gardens (Box 282)
      - Biological Station (Box 282)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 282)
      - Herbarium (Box 282)
    - Institutes
      - General (Box 282)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 282)
      - Mental Retardation (Box 282)
      - Science and Technology (Box 282)
      - Social Research (Box 282)
    - Committees
      - General (Box 282)
      - College Priorities (Box 282)
      - Human Subjects Committee (Box 282)
      - Library Committee (Box 282)
      - Statistical Instruction (Box 282)
      - Tropical Studies Committee (Box 282)
  - 1978/79
    - Topical Files
      - A (Box 282)
      - Admissions (Box 282)
      - Affirmative Action Program (Box 282)
      - Alumni (Box 282)
      - American Association of University Professors (Box 282)
      - Appeal procedures (Box 282)
      - Appointments (Box 282)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 282)
      - Associate Deanship (Box 282)
      - Awards (Box 282)
      - Black History (Box 282)
      - Budget (Box 282)
      - C (Box 282)
      - Camp David Seminar (Box 282)
      - Capital Planning (Box 282)
      - Career Planning and Placement (Box 282)
      - Catlin, Jamie (Box 282)
      - Chairman’s Meetings (Box 282)
      - CIC (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 282)
      - Classrooms (Box 282)
      - Closed Courses (Box 283)
      - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science (CIVS) (Box 283)
      - Collegiate Professors (Box 283)
      - Continuing Education of Women (Box 283)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 283)
      - Counseling (Box 283)
      - Course Evaluation (Box 283)
      - CRISP (Box 283)
      - Curriculum (Box 283)
      - D (Box 283)
      - Dean's Ear (Box 283)
      - Degrees (Box 283)
      - Development Office (Box 283)
      - DNA (Box 283)
      - Education, School of (Box 283)
      - Edwards, Mary (Box 283)
      - Emeritus (Box 283)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 283)
      - Enrollments (Box 283)
      - Environment (Box 283)
      - Equipment and Renovation (Box 283)
      - Executive Committee (Box 283)
      - Faculty (Box 283)
      - Faculty Code (Box 283)
      - Faculty Development (Box 283)
      - Faculty Exchange (Box 283)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 283)
      - Financial Aid (Box 283)
      - Fleming, Robben W. (Box 283)
      - Freedom of Information (Box 283)
      - Freshman Seminars (Box 283)
      - Galler, Bernard A. (Box 283)
      - Gerontology (Box 283)
      - Gifts Received (Box 283)
      - Grading (Box 283)
      - Graduate School (Box 283)
      - Graduate Student Assistants (Box 283)
      - Graduations Requirements Commission (Box 283)
      - Honors (Box 283)
      - Honors Convocations (Box 283)
      - Inteflex (Box 284)
      - Interdisciplinary Programs (Box 284)
      - Internship (Box 284)
      - Jackson, Marion (Box 284)
      - Knott, John (Box 284)
      - Lecturers (Box 284)
      - Ledbetter, Robert (Box 284)
      - Libraries, University (Box 284)
      - Long Range Planning (Box 284)
      - LS&A Magazine (Box 284)
      - Master's Programs (Box 284)
      - Medical School (Box 284)
      - Memorials (Box 284)
      - Michigan Daily (Box 284)
      - N (Box 284)
      - O (Box 284)
      - Organization Chart (Box 284)
      - Overberger, Charles G. (Box 284)
      - Personnel (Box 284)
      - Pharmacy, College of (Box 284)
      - Position Requests (Box 284)
      - Power, Eugene (Box 284)
      - President, Report to the (Box 284)
      - Priority Fund (Box 284)
      - Promotions (Box 284)
      - Publications (Box 284)
      - Rasmussen, Paul (Box 284)
      - Registrar, Office of (Box 284)
      - Research (Box 284)
      - Retirements (Box 284)
      - ROTC (Box 284)
      - Sabbaticals (Box 284)
      - Salaries (Box 284)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 284)
      - Senior Professor Lecture Series (Box 284)
      - Shapiro, Harold (Box 284)
      - Smith, Allan (Box 285)
      - Space (Box 285)
      - Staff (Box 285)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 285)
      - Students (Box 285)
      - Study Abroad (Box 285)
      - Teaching (Box 285)
      - Tenure (Box 285)
      - Travel (Box 285)
      - U-V (Box 285)
      - W-Z (Box 285)
      - Walgreen Professorship Committee (Box 285)
      - Women (Box 285)
      - Year of the Child (Box 285)
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 285)
      - Astronomy (Box 285)
      - Biological Sciences
        - General (Box 285)
        - Review (Box 285)
      - Chemistry (Box 285)
      - Classical Studies (Box 285)
      - Computer and Communication Sciences
        - General (Box 285)
        - Michael Conrad File (Box 285)
      - Economics (Box 285)
      - English
        - General (Box 285)
        - Review (Box 286)
        - Mary Rucker file, 2 folders (Box 286)
      - English Language Institute (Box 286)
      - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 286)
      - Geography (Box 286)
      - Geology and Mineralogy (Box 286)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 286)
      - History (Box 286)
      - History of Art (Box 286)
      - Journalism (Box 286)
      - Linguistics (Box 286)
      - Mathematics
        - General (Box 286)
        - Mathematics Institute (Box 286)
        - Review (Box 286)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 286)
      - Philosophy (Box 286)
      - Physics
        - General (Box 286)
        - Long-Range Plan (Box 286)
      - Political Science (Box 287)
        - General (Box 287)
        - Joel Samoff grievance (Box 287)
        - Frances Svensson file (Box 287)
      - Psychology (Box 287)
      - Residential College (Box 287)
      - Romance Languages
        - General (Box 287)
        - Review (Box 287)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 287)
      - Sociology (Box 287)
      - Speech Communication and Theatre
        - General (Proposed Department of Communications), 2 folders (Box 287)
        - Theatre (New Department of Theatre), 2 folders (Box 287)
      - Statistics (Box 287)
    - Centers/Programs
      - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 287)
      - American Culture (Box 287)
      - American Studies (Native) (Box 287)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 287)
      - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills (Box 287)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 288)
      - East Asian Studies (Box 288)
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 288)
      - English Composition Board (Box 288)
      - Film and Video (Box 288)
      - Great Books (Box 288)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 288)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 288)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (Box 288)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 288)
      - Near Eastern and North African Studies (Box 288)
      - Pilot Program (Box 288)
      - Population Studies (Box 288)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 288)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Box 288)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 288)
      - Western European Studies (Box 288)
      - Women's Studies (Box 288)
    - Museums
      - Anthropology (Box 288)
      - Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 288)
      - Art (Box 288)
      - Paleontology (Box 288)
      - Zoology (Box 288)
    - Laboratories/Gardens
      - Biological Station (Box 288)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 288)
      - Herbarium (Box 288)
    - Institutes
      - Mental Retardation (Box 288)
      - Public Policy Studies (Box 288)
      - Science and Technology (Box 288)
      - Social Research (Box 288)
    - Committees
      - General (Box 288)
  - 1979/80
    - Topical Files
      - A (Box 288)
      - Accounts (Box 288)
      - Adjunct Research Professor (Box 288)
      - Admissions (Box 288)
      - Affirmative Action Program (Box 288)
      - Alumni (Box 288)
      - Annual Five-Year Unit Profile (Box 288)
      - Appeal Procedures (Box 288)
      - Appointments (Box 288)
      - Armenian Studies (Box 288)
      - Associate Deanship (Box 288)
      - Associate Dean: Eric Rabkin (Box 288)
      - Associate Dean: Paul Rasmussen (Box 288)
      - Associate Dean: Jens Zorn (Box 288)
      - Athletics (Box 288)
      - Awards
        - General (Box 288)
        - Scholarships (Box 288)
        - Class of 1923 (Box 288)
        - Hopwood Awards (Box 288)
        - Ruth Sinclair Awards (Box 288)
      - B (Box 289)
      - Budget (Box 289)
      - C (Box 289)
      - Capital Campaign (Box 289)
      - Chairman’s Meetings (Box 289)
      - China Task Force (Box 289)
      - CIC (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 289)
      - Closed Courses (Box 289)
      - Collegiate Institute for Values and Science (CIVS) (Box 289)
      - Collegiate Professors (Box 289)
      - Continuing Education of Women (Box 289)
      - Cook Lectureship (Box 289)
      - Cost Sharing (Box 289)
      - Council of Colleges of Arts and Sciences (Box 289)
      - Counseling (Box 289)
      - Counseling Center (Box 289)
      - Course evaluation (Box 289)
      - Curriculum (Box 289)
      - D (Box 289)
      - Dean's Club (Box 289)
      - Dean's Ear (Box 289)
      - Deanship Search (Box 289)
      - Development Office (Box 289)
      - E (Box 289)
      - Education, School of (Box 289)
      - Edwards, Mary (Box 289)
      - Elections (Box 289)
      - Emeritus (Box 289)
      - Energy (Box 289)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 290)
      - Enrollments (Box 290)
      - Environment (Box 290)
      - Equipment and Renovation (Box 290)
      - Executive Committee (Box 290)
      - Faculty (Box 290)
      - Faculty Code (Box 290)
      - Faculty Development (Box 290)
      - Faculty Exchange (Box 290)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 290)
      - Final Exam Committee (Box 290)
      - Financial Aid (Box 290)
      - Freedom of Information (Box 290)
      - Freshman seminars (Box 290)
      - Gerontology (Box 290)
      - Gifts Received (Box 290)
      - Grading (Box 290)
      - Graduate School (Box 290)
      - Graduate Student Assistants (Box 290)
      - Graduation (Box 290)
      - Haber, William (Box 290)
      - Hewlett Foundation (Box 290)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 290)
      - Honors (Box 290)
      - Human Growth and Development (Box 290)
      - Inauguration (Box 290)
      - Inteflex (Box 290)
      - Interdisciplinary Programs (Box 290)
      - International Center (Box 290)
      - International Studies (Box 290)
      - Internship (Box 290)
      - Iranian Situation (Box 290)
      - Jackson, Marion (Box 290)
      - Johnson, Henry (Box 290)
      - Kellogg Visit (Box 290)
      - Knott, John (Box 290)
      - Lecturers (Box 290)
      - Leverette, Bland (Box 290)
      - Libraries, University (Box 290)
      - Long Range Planning (Box 290)
      - LS&A Magazine (Box 290)
      - M (Box 290)
      - MacInnes, Margo (Box 290)
      - Media (Box 290)
      - Medical School (Box 290)
      - Memorials (Box 291)
      - Minorities (Box 291)
      - Muir, Roy (Box 291)
      - "New Concept" Special Services (Box 291)
      - North Central Association (Box 291)
      - O (Box 291)
      - Organization Chart (Box 291)
      - Overberger, Charles G. (Box 291)
      - P (Box 291)
      - Personnel (Box 291)
      - Position Requests (Box 291)
      - President's Club (Box 291)
      - President's Report (Box 291)
      - Presidential Search (Box 291)
      - Primary Research Staff (Box 291)
      - Priority Fund (Box 291)
      - Program Evaluation (Box 291)
      - Promotions (Box 291)
      - Public Health, School of (Box 291)
      - Publications (Box 291)
      - Radock, Michael (Box 291)
      - Regents (Box 291)
      - Registrar, Office of (Box 291)
      - Research (Box 291)
      - Retirements (Box 291)
      - ROTC (Box 291)
      - S (Box 291)
      - Sabbaticals (Box 291)
      - Salaries (Box 291)
      - Scheduling (Box 292)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 292)
      - Senior Professor Lecture Series (Box 292)
      - Shapiro, Harold (Box 292)
      - Smith, Allan (Box 292)
      - Social Events (Box 292)
      - Social Sciences (Box 292)
      - Social Work, School of (Box 292)
      - Space (Box 292)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 292)
      - Student Government (Box 292)
      - Students (Box 292)
      - Study Abroad (Box 292)
      - Summer Sessions, Association of (Box 292)
      - Sussman, Al (Box 292)
      - Teaching (Box 292)
      - Tenure (Box 292)
      - Travel (Box 292)
      - University Professorships (Box 292)
      - V (Box 292)
      - Vice-Presidential Search (Box 292)
      - Walgreen Professorship Committee (Box 292)
      - Women (Box 292)
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 292)
      - Astronomy (Box 292)
      - Biological Sciences
        - General (Box 292)
        - Amphibian Facility (Box 292)
      - Chemistry (Box 292)
      - Classical Studies (Box 292)
      - Communications (Box 292)
      - Computer and Communication Sciences
        - General (Box 292)
        - Review (Box 292)
      - Economics (Box 293)
        - General (Box 293)
        - Gary Saxonhouse File (Box 293)
      - English (Box 293)
      - English Language Institute (Box 293)
      - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures (Box 293)
      - Geography (Box 293)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 293)
      - Germanic Languages and Literatures (Box 293)
      - History of Art (Box 293)
      - Linguistics (Box 293)
      - Mathematics (Box 293)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 293)
      - Philosophy (Box 293)
      - Physics (Box 293)
      - Political Science (Box 293)
      - Psychology (Box 294)
      - Residential College (Box 294)
      - Romance Languages (Box 294)
      - Slavic Languages and Literatures (Box 294)
      - Sociology (Box 294)
      - Statistics (Box 294)
      - Theatre and Drama
        - General (Box 294)
        - Theatre Search Committee (Box 294)
    - Centers/Programs
      - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 294)
      - American Culture (Box 294)
      - Chinese Center (Box 294)
      - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills (Box 294)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 294)
      - East Asian Studies (Box 294)
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 294)
      - English Composition Board (Box 294)
      - Film and Video (Box 294)
      - Great Books (Box 294)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 294)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 294)
      - Language Laboratory (Box 294)
      - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 294)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (Box 294)
      - Middle English Dictionary (Box 294)
      - Near Eastern and North African Studies (Box 294)
      - Pilot Program (Box 294)
      - Population Studies (Box 294)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 294)
      - Russian and Eastern European Studies (Box 294)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 294)
      - Western European Studies (Box 294)
      - Women's Studies (Box 295)
        - General (Box 295)
        - Review (Box 295)
    - Museums
      - Anthropology (Box 295)
      - Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 295)
      - Art (Box 295)
      - Exhibit (Box 295)
      - Museum libraries (Box 295)
      - Paleontology (Box 295)
      - Zoology
        - General (Box 295)
        - Review (Box 295)
    - Laboratories/Gardens
      - Biological Station
        - General (Box 295)
        - Review (Box 295)
      - Botanical Gardens (Box 295)
      - Herbarium
        - General (Box 295)
        - Review (Box 295)
    - Institutes
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 295)
      - Mental Retardation (Box 295)
      - Public Policy Studies (Box 295)
      - Science and Technology (Box 295)
      - Social Research (Box 295)
      - Committees: General (Box 295)
    - Miscellaneous multiple year files
      - 1970s-1980s (Box 295)
        (includes files relating to the closing of the Center for Research on Conflict Resolution)
  - 1980/81
    - Topical Files
      - A (Box 305)
      - Admissions (Office of) and Admissions Committees (Box 305)
      - Affirmative Action Program (Box 305)
      - Awards
        - General (Box 305)
        - Class of 1923 (Box 305)
      - B (Box 305)
      - Budget (Box 305)
      - Budget Reductions: Other Colleges and Schools (Box 305)
      - C (Box 305)
      - Capital Campaign (Box 305)
      - Chairman’s and Directors' Meetings (Box 305)
      - CIC (Committee on Institutional Cooperation) (Box 305)
      - Congratulatory Letters (Box 305)
      - Counseling (Box 305)
      - Curriculum (Box 305)
      - D (Box 305)
      - Deanship Search (Box 305)
      - Degrees (Box 305)
      - Development Office (Box 305)
      - Distinguished Professors (Box 305)
      - E (Box 305)
      - Education, School of (Box 305)
      - Emeritus (Box 305)
      - Endowed Chairs (Box 305)
      - Engineering, College of (Box 305)
      - Enrollments (Box 305)
      - Environment (Box 305)
      - Equipment and Renovation (Box 305)
      - Executive Committee (Box 305)
      - F (Box 305)
      - Faculty (Box 305)
      - Faculty Meetings (Box 305)
      - Faculty Reduction (Box 306)
      - Faculty Replacement (Box 306)
      - Freeze on Positions (Box 306)
      - Freshman Seminars (Box 306)
      - Frye, Billy E. (Vice President for Academic Affairs) (Box 306)
      - G (Box 306)
      - Graduate Student Assistants
        - General (Box 306)
        - Ten Term Rule (Box 306)
      - Graduate Studies (Rackham) (Box 306)
      - H (Box 306)
      - Honorary Degrees (Box 306)
      - Honors Program (Box 306)
      - I (Box 306)
      - Inteflex (Box 306)
      - Internship (Box 306)
      - L (Box 306)
      - Lecturers (Box 306)
      - Library (Box 306)
      - Long Range Planning (Box 306)
      - LS&A Magazine (Box 306)
      - M (Box 306)
      - Media (Box 306)
      - Medical School (Box 306)
      - Melchiori, Gerlinda (Box 306)
      - Mellon Foundation (Box 306)
      - Memorials (Box 306)
      - Minorities (Box 306)
      - Mississippi Valley Deans (Box 306)
      - Muir, Roy (Box 306)
      - Natural Resources (Box 306)
      - Netherlands Visiting Professorship (Box 306)
      - North Central Association (Box 306)
      - O (Box 306)
      - Overberger, Charles G. (Box 306)
      - P (Box 306)
      - Personnel (Box 306)
      - Position Requests (Box 306)
      - Power, Eugene (Box 306)
      - President's Club (Box 306)
      - President's Report (Box 306)
      - Priority Fund (Box 307)
      - Program Evaluation, Review, or Reduction (Box 307)
      - Program Reduction (Box 307)
      - Promotions (Box 307)
      - Publications (Box 307)
      - R (Box 307)
      - Regents (Box 307)
      - Research (Box 307)
      - Retirements (Box 307)
      - Reviews (Box 307)
      - S (Box 307)
      - Sabbaticals (Box 307)
      - Salaries (Box 307)
      - Schaper, David (Box 307)
      - Scheduling (Box 307)
      - Senate Assembly (Box 307)
      - Shapiro, Harold (Box 307)
      - SOUP (Box 307)
        (informal discussion re: "smaller but better university")
      - Space (Box 307)
      - Staff Meetings (Box 307)
      - Student Governance (Box 307)
      - Students (Box 307)
      - Study Abroad (Box 307)
      - T (Box 308)
      - Teaching (Box 308)
      - Tenure (Box 308)
      - Thurnau Funds (Box 308)
      - Travel (Box 308)
      - Visitor Suites (Box 308)
      - Walgreen Chair (Box 308)
      - Women (Box 308)
    - Departments
      - Anthropology (Box 308)
      - Astronomy (Box 308)
      - Biological Sciences
        - General (Box 308)
        - Review, 2 folders (Box 308)
      - Chemistry (Box 308)
      - Classical Studies (Box 308)
      - Communications (Box 308)
      - Computer and Communication Sciences (CCS)
        - General (Box 308)
        - Chairmanship Search (Box 308)
      - Economics (Box 308)
      - English Language and Literature (Box 308)
      - English Language Institute (Box 308)
      - Far Eastern Languages (Box 308)
      - Geography
        - Discontinuance, 1 folders (Box 308)
        - Discontinuance, 3 folders (Box 309)
        - Review (Box 309)
      - Geological Sciences (Box 309)
      - Germanic Languages (Box 309)
      - History, 2 folders (Box 309)
      - History of Art (Box 309)
      - Linguistics
        - General (Box 309)
        - Evaluation Committee, Report of (Box 309)
        - Review Committee (Box 309)
      - Mathematics (Box 309)
      - Near Eastern Studies (Box 310)
      - Philosophy (Box 310)
      - Physics (Box 310)
      - Political Science (Box 310)
      - Psychology
        - General (Box 310)
        - Center for Cognitive Science (Box 310)
      - Residential College
        - General (Box 310)
        - Report 1977-1981 (Box 310)
      - Romance Languages (Box 310)
      - Slavic Languages (Box 310)
      - Sociology (Box 310)
      - Statistics (Box 310)
      - Theatre (Box 310)
    - Centers/Programs
      - Afro-American and African Studies (Box 310)
      - American Culture (Box 310)
      - American Institutions (Box 310)
      - Area Studies (Box 310)
      - Asian Studies (Box 310)
      - Chinese Studies (Box 310)
      - Coalition for the Use of Learning Skills
        - General (Box 310)
        - Review (Box 311)
      - Comparative Literature (Box 311)
      - Economic Development, Center for Research on (Box 311)
      - English Composition Board (Box 311)
      - Film and Video (Box 311)
      - Great Books (Box 311)
      - Japanese Studies (Box 311)
      - Judaic Studies (Box 311)
      - Language Laboratory (Box 311)
      - Learning and Teaching, Center for Research on (Box 311)
      - Medieval and Renaissance Collegium (Box 311)
      - Near Eastern and North African Studies (Box 311)
      - Pilot Program (Box 311)
      - Population Studies (Box 311)
      - South and Southeast Asian Studies (Box 311)
      - Western European Studies (Box 311)
      - Women's Studies (Box 311)
    - Museums
      - General (Box 311)
      - Anthropology (Box 311)
      - Archaeology (Kelsey Museum) (Box 311)
      - Art (Box 311)
      - Exhibit (Box 311)
      - Paleontology (Box 311)
      - Zoology (Box 311)
    - Laboratories/Gardens
      - Biological Station (Box 311)
      - Botanical Gardens
        - General (Box 311)
        - Evaluation Report (Box 311)
        - Reduction and Review (Box 311)
      - Herbarium
        - General (Box 311)
        - Review (Box 311)
    - Institutes
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 311)
      - Mental Retardation and Related Disabilities (Box 311)
      - Science and Technology (Box 311)
      - Social Research (Box 311)
    - Committees
      - General (Box 311)
      - Admissions Steering Committee (Box 311)
      - Joint Faculty/Student Policy (Box 311)
      - Statistical Instruction (Box 311)
  - 1981/82
    - Topical Files
      - Accounts (Box 312)
      - Admissions (Office of) and Admissions Committees (Box 312)
      - Affirmative Action (Box 312)